# **SARAH TRUONG**

# **UI/UX** Designer

struongux.com

struong428@gmail.com

813.810.9913

# **EDUCATION**

# A.S. Graphic & Interactive Design

Valencia College Sep 2015 - Dec 2017 Orlando, FL

#### **B.S. Microbiology**

University of Georgia Aug 2011 - May 2015 Athens, GA

**Zell Miller Scholarship** 

#### **SKILLS**

# Design

Adobe Suite Sketch Balsamiq InVision Prototyping Web Design User Research

Usability Testing

A/B Testing

#### **Development**

HTML 5 / CSS 3 Basic Javascript Jquery

# **Digital Marketing**

Email Marketing Basic SEO MailChimp Google Analytics

#### **LEADERSHIP**

#### Co-President

UGA Japan Club 2013 - 2014

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a UI/UX designer that is design, data, and user driven. With a background in both science and interactive design, I strive to create innovative solutions to better user experiences through aesthetics and problem-solving. Willing to relocate.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **UI/UX Designer**

ConnectWise

Oct 2019 - Present | Tampa, FL

- Refine user experiences and design wireframes, mockups, and interactive prototypes for software and mobile apps
- Perform user research and usability sessions with key stakeholders and partners

### **Digital Designer**

**Westgate Resorts** 

Jul 2018 - Present | Orlando, FL

- Designed marketing collateral and high-fidelity prototypes for website redesigns to increase conversions
- Established design library and improved design process and workflow for projects to make production more efficient

# **UI Designer**

StrategyBeam

Oct 2018 - Feb 2019 | Orlando, FL

- · Created digital assets, wireframes, and mock-ups for website
- Provided UI solutions to business goals to increase conversion rates and leads for website redesigns

#### **Web Design Intern**

**Ripley Entertainment** 

Feb 2018 - Aug 2018 | Orlando, FL

- Redesigned and optimized WordPress websites to ensure a positive user experience through design and functionality
- Designed email newsletters for email marketing and digital assets for social media marketing, ads & promotions

#### Freelancer

Self-employed

June 2016 - July 2017 | Orlando, FL

- Consulted with local businesses to provide design solutions and solve users' needs through user research, information design, interaction design, visual design and prototyping
- Created marketing collateral posters, banners, menus, pamphlets, photo editing, responsive web layouts, user studies and UI design